<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wittyape</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign-In</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign-Up</string>
    <string name="helping_kids_excel">Helping Kids Excel</string>
    <string name="wittyape">Wittyape</string>
    <string name="display_name">Display Name</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account_yet">Don\'t have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="master_mathematics">Master Mathematics</string>
    <string name="mathematics">Mathematics</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="open">Oepn</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="help">Help &amp; feedback</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="learn">Learn</string>
    <string name="profile">Wittyape Profile</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="primary">Primary</string>
    <string name="counting">Counting</string>
    <string name="addition">Addition</string>
    <string name="subtraction">Subtraction</string>
    <string name="ready_to_learn">Ready to learn?</string>
    <string name="choose_class">Select your class</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="loading_display_name">Loading display name</string>
    <string name="practice">Practice</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="practice_couting">Practice Couting</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="question">Question?</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="correct_answer">Correct Answer:</string>
    <string name="total_questions">Total Questions:</string>
    <string name="accuracy">Accuracy</string>
    <string name="performace">Performace</string>
    <string name="practice_addition">Practice Addition</string>
    <string name="practice_subtraction">Practice Subtraction</string>
    <string name="practice_multiplication">Practice Multiplication</string>
    <string name="addition_text_1">Addition is bringing two or more numbers (or things) together to make a new total</string>
    <string name="addition_text_2">Here 2 balls are added to 1 ball to make 3 balls</string>
    <string name="addition_text_3">In Numerals : 2 + 1 = 3</string>
    <string name="addition_text_4">In Words : Two plus one equals three</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_1">Subtraction is taking one number away from another.</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_2">Say you had 3 balls</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_3">Your friend borrowed this red ball</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_4">Now you have green and blue ball</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_5">In Numerals : 3 – 1 = 2</string>
    <string name="subtraction_text_6">In Words : Three minus one equals two</string>
    <string name="equals_symbol">=</string>
    <string name="add_symbol">+</string>
    <string name="leaderboard">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="loading">loading</string>
    <string name="top_scorer">Top Scorer</string>
    <string name="scoring_system">Scoring system</string>
    <string name="scoring_system_1">How to Score Points?</string>
    <string name="scoring_system_2">Mathematics:\n\nEach Right answer wins you one point.\nYou get 30 seconds to earn maximum points with right answers.\n\nEnglish:\n\nYou get one point on getting the right answer on your first attempt.\n\nNote: Active Internet Connection is needed to update and upload your score.\n\nScores of Top 10 students will be published on leaderboard.</string>
    <string name="multiplication">Multiplication</string>
    <string name="multiplication_text_1">Multiplication is one of the four elementary mathematical operations of arithmetic, with the other ones being addition, subtraction and division.\nThe basic idea of multiplication is repeated addition.</string>
    <string name="multiplication_text_2">Example: 3 × 2 = 3 + 3 = 6</string>
    <string name="multiplication_text_3">In Numerals : 3 × 2 = 6</string>
    <string name="multiplication_text_4">In Words : Three times two equals six</string>
    <string name="multiplication_times_two">x 2</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="practice_roman_numerals">Practice Roman Numerals</string>
    <string name="roman_numeral">Roman Numeral</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_1">Wittyape is a free self–driven learning management system that offers highly personalised and effective learning programs for classes 1 – 4 for CBSE, ICSE and other boards to help them learn by practice. The app and website provide multiple questions to learn and engage with their subject by solving interactive exercises to test their learning. Our products are carefully designed to ensure maximum learning through proven techniques such as adaptive learning.</string>
    <string name="mail_us">Mail us</string>
    <string name="have_feedback_or_query">Have feedback or query?</string>
    <string name="terms_condition">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_condition_1">PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. BY USING THIS PLATFORM YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL OF THE BELOW TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND PRIVACY POLICY.\n\n1. Terms of Service\n\nBy choosing to visit and/or avail any Services provided by Wittyape, you agree to these Terms (as may be amended from time to time). Please read the following information carefully. If you are a parent or guardian and you provide your consent to your child\'s use of the Platform, you agree to be bound by these Terms in respect to their use of the Platform. By your continued access or use of the Platform, you signify your agreement to be legally bound by the Terms set forth herein. If you do not agree to the Terms of this agreement, promptly exit this platform and stop accessing the Services.\n\n2. Description of Services\n\nWittyape facilitates online education services to children. We aim at providing lessons on Mathematics and English to the Child. The concept is to create a virtual classroom, which helps the Child to learn without any restrictions on time and place.\nWittyape will have its sets of modules according to which the Child is expected to complete their levels. Wittyape has lessons who will be assisting the Child with their modules.\nHowever, for accessing the Services, the Child or You may have to create an account and disclose ("Personal Information") including\n(i) name\n(ii) e-mail ID\n(iii) class\n\n3. License to Use\n\nWittyape hereby grants You and the Child the limited right to access, view and use the Platform only for the purposes of accessing, viewing, or submitting User material. Company reserves the right to suspend or deny, in its sole discretion, your access to all or any portion of the Platform. This license is limited to personal and non-commercial uses by You and your Child. Any rights not expressly granted to You herein are reserved to Wittyape.\n\n4. Intellectual Property Rights\n\nWittyape retains all rights (including copyrights, trademarks, patents, designs, logos, trade-dress, trade-secrets, know-how as well as any other intellectual property right) in relation to all information provided on or via this Platform (including but not limited to the curriculum taught, all texts, graphics, photos, illustrations, apps and logos). You shall not copy, publish, distribute or reproduce any of the information contained on this Platform or social media in any form without the prior written consent of Wittyape.\n\n5. Intended Purpose of Use\n\nAny application, code or content created using Wittyape’s platform are intended to be used solely as prototypes and for evaluation of validity and practicability of ideas. All such applications, codes and/or content may be solely created for educational purposes and gathering feedback by the students and are in no way fit for or meant to be used for any commercial use. Any other use of such apps, codes or content, other than the use specified herein is prohibited by Wittyape and the Wittyape shall not be liable for the same and you and your child shall indemnify Wittyape for any loss, claims or damages suffered by Wittyape in this regard.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_1">Information We Collect and use\n\nWe collect information including\n(i) name\n(ii) e-mail ID\n(iii) class\n\nPurpose of Collection\n\nWe collect personal information only necessary for the following purposes:\n\n1. To create and maintain an account;\n\n2. To enable you to avail of our Services, and ensure efficient customer care experience and develop new features;\n\n3. To determine the class of the Child and maintain his score in exercises.\n\nData Security\n\nWe always strive to keep your Personal Information safe, we have been taking many safety measures, including:\n\n1. The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n2. Safety in the operating environment: we store your Personal Information in a safe operating environment and it can only be accessed by employees, representatives and service providers on a need-to-use basis. We comply with industry standards and the law to protect your Personal Information.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_1">The information contained in this platform is for general educational purposes only. We make no representations or warranties of any kind, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the application/website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the application/website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.\nIn no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this application/website.</string>
    <string name="class_one">Class 1</string>
    <string name="class_one_syllabus_maths">Counting Numbers [1 to 30]\nAddition [Single digit numbers]\nSubtraction [Single digit numbers]</string>
    <string name="class_one_syllabus_english">Animal and their Babies\nOpposite words\nAdjectives</string>
    <string name="class_two">Class 2</string>
    <string name="class_two_syllabus_maths">Counting Numbers [1 to 100]\nRoman numerals [1 to 20]\nAddition [Double digit numbers]\nSubtraction [Double digit numbers]\nMultiplication [Single digit numbers, 1 to 4]</string>
    <string name="class_two_syllabus_english">Articles\nPlurals</string>
    <string name="class_three">Class 3</string>
    <string name="class_three_syllabus_maths">Addition [Double digit numbers]\nSubtraction [Double digit numbers]\nRoman numerals [1 to 50]\nMultiplication [Single digit numbers, 1 to 6]\nMultiplication table : [1 to 6]</string>
    <string name="class_three_syllabus_english">Animal sounds\nSilent letters</string>
    <string name="class_four">Class 4</string>
    <string name="class_four_syllabus_maths">Addition [Double digit numbers]\nSubtraction [Double digit numbers]\nRoman numerals [1 to 50]\nMultiplication table [1 to 10]</string>
    <string name="class_four_syllabus_english">Verbs\nDegree of Comparison</string>
    <string name="syllabus">Syllabus</string>
    <string name="multiplication_table">Multiplication Table</string>
    <string name="master_english">Master English</string>
    <string name="animal_and_their_babies">Animal and\ntheir Babies</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="check">Check</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="opposite_words">Antonyms</string>
    <string name="adjective">Adjectives</string>
    <string name="articles">Articles</string>
    <string name="plurals">Plurals</string>
    <string name="silent_nletters">Silent\nLetters</string>
    <string name="animal_nsounds">Animal\nSounds</string>
    <string name="silent_letters">Silent letters</string>
    <string name="animal_sounds">Animal sounds</string>
    <string name="verb">Verb</string>
    <string name="degrees_of_comparison">Degrees of\nComparison</string>
    <string name="question_english_animalbaby">Enter the baby name of the animal:</string>
    <string name="question_english_antonym">Enter the antonym of:</string>
    <string name="question_english_adjective">Find the adjective in the sentence:</string>
    <string name="question_english_articles">Identify the article in the sentence:</string>
    <string name="question_english_plural">Write down the plural of the word:</string>
    <string name="question_english_silentletter">Which letter is silent in the word:</string>
    <string name="question_english_animalsound">Write the name of sound this animal makes:</string>
    <string name="question_english_evrb">Identify the verb in the sentence:</string>
    <string name="question_english_comparison">Identify words with degree of comparison:</string>
    <string name="resource_english_animalbaby">Here’s a list of some baby animal names:\n\nCat - kitten\nTiger - cub\nDeer - fawn\nChicken - chick\nDog - puppy\nDuck - duckling\nLion - cub\nPig - piglet\nSheep - lamb\nMonkey - infant\n</string>
    <string name="resource_english_antonyms">Antonym is a word opposite in meaning to another.\n\nHere’s a list of a few antonyms-\n\nHot - Cold\nFew - Many\nEast - West\nMan - Woman\nWin - Lose\nBlack - White\nQuestion - Answer\nHard - Easy\nPoor - Rich\nLittle - Big\n</string>
    <string name="resource_english_adjective">A word that describes a noun or pronoun is an adjective.\nIn the sentence ‘This shop has the best samosas’, ‘best’ is an adjective.\n\nLet’s see a few more examples of how adjectives are used in sentences.\n\nThe dog found a large bone.\nlarge\nShe wore a beautiful dress.\nbeautiful\nShashi is a good man.\ngood\nThis glass is strong.\nstrong\nThis is a big box.\nbig\nMy job is worse than yours.\nworse\nShashi is really clever.\nclever\nThe doctor is late.\nlate\nThe house is bigger than other ones.\nbigger\nHe is angry.\nangry</string>
    <string name="resource_english_articles">"English has two articles: the and a/an. A/an is used to modify nouns, whereas the is used to refer to nouns.\n\nHere’s how we use them in sentences:\n\nUsing - a\n\nI need a book.\nThey bought a computer.\nMy friend has a pet dog.\nShe saw a movie last night.\n\nUsing - an\n\nShashi has an idea.\nShe ate an apple.\nI eat an apple everyday.\nHe is an honest person.\n\nUsing - the\n\nThe Moon rotates around the Earth.\nThe sun is brighter than the Moon "</string>
    <string name="resource_english_plural">Plural denotes a quantity more than one.\n\nHere’s a list of some few plural words:\n\nPuppy - puppies\nTooth - teeth\nMouse - mice\nMan - men\nWoman - women\nCity - cities\nSpy - spies\nBaby - babies\nWolf - wolves\nKnife - knives\n</string>
    <string name="resource_english_silent">A silent letter is a letter that does not correspond to any sound in the word\'s pronunciation.\n\nHere are a few examples of words with their silent letters.\n\nKnee - k\nTwo - w\nWhere - h\nNestle - t\nLamb - b\nBomb - b\nSchool - h\nHonest - h\nMatch - t\nListen - t\n</string>
    <string name="resource_english_animal_sound">Here’s a list of a some other animal sound names.\n\nFox - yelp\nBull - bellow\nBee - buzz\nOwl - hoot</string>
    <string name="resource_english_verb">Verbs are the action words in a sentence that describe what the subject is doing.\n\nTo help you understand with ease, we have identified verbs in the sentences.\n\nThe baby is playing with blocks.\nplaying\nMy mom cooks a yummy meal every day.\ncooks\nWe began to climb the hill.\nclimb\nShe is drawing a picture\ndrawing\nHe writes his name on the desk.\nwrites\nShe ran across the garden.\nran\nThe Sun rises from the East.\nrises\nBirds build their nests.\nbuild\nThey play with a ball.\nplay\nThe boy closed the door.\nclosed</string>
    <string name="resource_english_comparision">Adjectives describe a quality or characteristic of a noun or pronoun. The basic form of an adjective is known as positive degree.\nAdjectives can be changed to compare a quality between two nouns, this form is known as the comparative degree.\nWe can also change an adjective to identify a noun with the highest degree of an attribute among a group, this is known as the superlative degree.\n\nExample of Positive to Comparative degree\n\nTall - more tall\nBig - bigger\nSmall - smaller\n\nExample of Positive to Superlative degree\n\nTall - tallest\nBig - biggest\nSmall - smallest</string>
    <string name="cat_meow">Cat - Meow</string>
    <string name="cow_moo">Cow - Moo</string>
    <string name="crow_caw">Crow - Caw</string>
    <string name="dog_bark">Dog - Bark</string>
    <string name="duck_quack">Duck - Quack</string>
    <string name="wolf_howl">Wolf - Howl</string>
    <string-array name="class_selector">]
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Class1</item>
        <item>Class2</item>
        <item>Class3</item>
        <item>Class4</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>